nolimitvids.com 2013-03-05

# No Limit Vids - Unlimited XXX DVD Downloads Instantly

Your privacy is important to us. **No personal information will be shared with any third parties without the customer’s permission** To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

The Information We Collect: we collect email addresses on the signup page for the use of sending emails to our customers with special offers as well as their username/password and country if they signup to one of our sites.

Customers credit card details are NEVER stored on our servers, this data is collected and processed through our billing gateway Netbilling.com. Netbilling.com is specially tasked and authorized to collect & process customer credit cards and are authorized to keep such customer data. We do collect the customers username, password, country & email address but this is only temporary for use in cascading billing. The customers username & password, country & email address is only stored on a permanent basis at our secured servers if the customer decides to join one of our sites with his credit card.

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on our company websites. On some pages, you can order products/subscriptions, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

  * Name:
  * Address:
  * Email address:
  * Phone number:

**The Way We Use Information:**  
We use the infomation for processing the customers signup via check or credit card to our site, we collect email addresses for future special offers to be sent to customer as well as to send the customer his/her username & password after signup process is approved. The customers name, address, phone & other details are used to cascade between billing processors to help the customer signup to our site, if the customer does not signup to any of our processors or checking processors/web900. Then the customers data except for email address is deleted.

**Our Commitment To Data Security:**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information:**  
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by [description of the company access procedure]. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**How To Contact Us:**  
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at [[support@nolimitvids.com](mailto:support@nolimitvids.com)].

To view the privacy policy of our Gateway credit card processing company : Netbilling.com please visit : <http://www.netbilling.com/privacy.php>
